本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：Joanna      校对：小路     时间轴：虫不知
特效：Will      后期：冰河       监制：蛐蛐
■
怎么了
What's up?
要买什么吗
What you need?
是买货还是停下来看我好看啊
Yo, you buying, or are you just stopping to envy?
这帮傻逼
Punk bitches.
本机号码505-1275223请留言
Please leave your message for 505-1275223.
请在提示音声后留言  发信息请拨...
Record your message after the tone.To send a numeric page...
闪开  小鬼
Bounce, little man.
瘦子  我现在在第二大道和黑兹尔坦路交叉口
Yo,Skinny, I'm up on 2nd and Hazeltine,
被人盯上了
Getting eyeballed hard.
有点不对劲  兄弟  快来帮我
I got a bad feeling, man.I need some backup.
尽快赶来
Get your ass up here now.
你耳朵上那是啥
What's that thing in your ear?
我怎么跟你说的  闪开
What did I say? Get out of here!
还在瞎磨蹭什么  快走
What are you waiting for? Go!
绝
命
毒
师
第二季
第十一集
治疗已经初见成效
We've made such headway with your treatments
是时候讨论下接下来的治疗计划了
That now it's time we talked about sealing the deal.
当然
Absolutely.
你们知道的
As you know,
最初的诊断是说你的癌症不适于手术
My initial diagnosis was that your cancer was inoperable.
现在情况不一样了
That may no longer be the case.
我们认为目前来说肺叶切除手术是可取之选
We think now that a lobectomy may be a viable option.
也许还是个非常不错的选择
Maybe a pretty good option.
布冯尼克医生是国内为数不多的
Dr. Bravenec is one of the few surgeons in the country
能实施全剂量放疗后肺叶切除术的医生之一
Performing lobectomies after full-dosage radiation.
且手术成功率很高
He's got a good track record.
成功率颇高
Pretty good.
听上去
It sounds...
很不错
Aggressive.
对  正是这样
Yes. Very much so.
你们要知道  如果不动这个手术
Understand that if you don't have this surgery,
就只能眼睁睁等着癌细胞扩散
You're just waiting for the cancer to spread.
这是一定的
And it will.
现在  通过之前的治疗
Now,through the treatment you've had already,
我们给你争取了点时间
We've bought you some time...
也许很久  也可能很短
Maybe a lot, probably a little,
但也就如此而已
But that's all.
在我看来
In my opinion,
如果你愿意冒险一试
If you're willing to take some risk,
那这就是最好的机会了
Then this offers the best chance.
治疗费用要多少
How much would it cost?
我没有医疗保险
I'm not on your insurance.
我算下来  总共费用
I'd say between 170,000
大概17万到20万
And 200,000, all in.
我这部分的费用  我当然愿意帮你尽量减免
For my part, I'd be willing to write off what I can,
但最花钱的并不是我这部分
But mine isn't even the biggest expense.
当然  这是个重大决定
This is obviously a big decision.
两位应该会想好好商量一下
And you folks are gonna want to take some time to discuss it.
不用了
No.
我接受手术
I'll do it.
沃尔特 你不觉得我们至少该先商量商量吗
Walt, don't you think we should at least talk this through first?
我只是觉得这是个办法
I just think it's the way to go.
我不得不说  你做出了正确的选择
I have to say I think It's the right choice.
我建议我们再等上两周  让肺炎痊愈
I recommend we let the pneumonitis heal for couple of weeks,
然后就进行手术
And then we'll have at it.
这恐怕不行  我...
That's tricky.I...
-预产期什么时候  -21号
- When's the due date? - It's the 21st.
还有两周就生了
So two weeks and change?
我把手术排在四周之后
I'll book the surgery for four weeks from now.
那样的话
That way,
沃尔特能亲自迎接女儿的降生
Walter can be on his feet for the birth of your daughter.
但不能再拖下去了
But I wouldn't wait any longer.
14条短信...
14 messag...
天哪
God.
喂
Yeah
是我
It's me.
你TM去哪了  我打了不下20个电话找你
Where the hell were you?I called, like, 20 times.
在忙
Working.
什么事
What is it?
康宝死了
Combo's dead.
枪杀的
Shot.
他是哪个
Which one is he?
你不会就来这么一句吧
You did not just say that to me.
-杰西  听着  -我就知道会这样
- Jesse, listen... - That figures.
外面的人都怎么说
What's the word on the street?
没人看到  不知道谁干的
No one's dropping no names.
康宝出事前给我打过电话
Combo rang me before it went down.
说被人盯上了
Said dudes were mad-dogging him,
把他逼到了街角  我就知道这些
Trying to run him up off the corner.That's all I know.
我们为啥得急着扩展地盘  我是说
Why'd we have to go pushing into new turf, yo? I mean,
你到底想做什么
What'd you expect?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道
You don't know?
你就会说这么一句吗
Is that all you got?
我会安置好康宝的家人
I'll do right by Combo's people.
你得记着把你手机砸了扔了
Make sure you bust up your cell and toss it.
我们会找到凶手的
We'll figure it out.
我很感激你能这么说
I appreciate what you're saying and all,
但康宝死了  猴子又去了卡利避风头
But with Combo gone and Badger laying low out in Cali...
我还在缓刑期呢  伙计
I'm on probation, man.
随时都可能被抓进去
Fast track to Los Lunas.
我们眼看着
We're on the verge
就能赚到大笔大笔的银子  瘦子
Of making some serious coin.Skinny.
怎么  你现在想收手不干吗
What, you're gonna jump ship now?
俗话说
This game we playing,
没有金刚钻别揽瓷器活
We don't got the street cred to survive it.
要是放在以前  大家都以为是你杀了精虫
Back when everyone thought you killed Spooge,
也许我们还有戏
Maybe we were doing okay,
但那件事...
But that whole...
用自动取款机砸人脑袋那事
Thing to the head thing, the ATM?
他那吸毒的婊子都招了
His junkie bitch copped to it.
全城的人都知道不是你干的了
The whole town knows it wasn't you.
大家都知道了
Everyone knows?
你为什么不早说
Why didn't you say something?
我不知道
I don't know, man.
因为我们都喜欢你吧
'Cause we like you and all.
我跟你说  你等着瞧好了
I'm telling you, just sit tight.
我们会没事的
We'll get by.
我们能成的
We'll make it.
杰西  抱歉
Sorry, Jesse.
我不干了
I'm out.
我们遇到了点小挫折
We have had a bit of a setback.
抱歉  事实就是如此
Sorry, that's an accurate description.
你还想让我怎么说
What else do you want me to call it?
认个错怎么样  说你做错了
How about your fault? How about that?
别赖我头上
Don't lay that on me.
负责销售的人是你
You are in charge of distribution.
是你说要扩张地盘的
You said expand the territory.
-那我也没让你们这么不小心啊  -两位  两位
- That doesn't mean you become careless.- Guys, guys!
你们以为这是上脱口秀呢
Who do I look like, Maury Povich?
我也不是你们的婚姻顾问
I'm not your marriage counselor.
你们都是行家  拿点样子出来
Now, you're professionals.Act like it.
遇到点小挫折  继续
Now, setback. Go.
我们有个毒贩被杀了
One of our dealers was murdered.
就像地盘争夺战一样
It was some kind of turf dispute,
很显然  我们输了
And apparently we lost.
然后我们的人都不干了
And then everyone quit on us.
我们的货完全动不了
We have absolutely no distribution.
那这些事有没有可能追查到你们头上
Is there any way any of this can be traced back to you?
我说的是警察
Now, the police, I'm talking about.
这真是不幸中的万幸
There's your silver lining.
你呢  健康状况如何
How about you?How's the health situation?
好点了  别抽了行不
It's better.Do you mind?
好点了
Better?
治疗看起来效果不错
It's looking a little more positive.
我剩下的时间比我预想的多
I may have more time than I thought.
非常好
Outstanding.
说起那个死掉的
Now, as to your dead guy,
干这行难免的
Occupational hazard.
毒贩挨枪子
Drug dealer getting shot,
我就直说吧
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
这是明摆着的
And say it's been known to happen.
你们手头的货呢  还有多少存货
Now, what about product on hand?How's your inventory?
38多点
38 and change.
38盎司[1KG多点]  还是38克
38 ounces? Grams?
38磅[17KG多]
Pounds.
你说过让我们别坐失良机
You did say make hay while the sun is shining.
两位
Guys!
干嘛还拉长个脸
Why the long faces here?
你们简直坐拥金山啊
You're sitting on a gold mine.
坐拥金山却卖不出去
A gold mine we can't sell.
我们需要严密的组织结构
We need a proper infrastructure.
需要在街头有靠得住的
We need foot soldiers and dealers
毒贩销售网络
On a street level that are rock solid.
我们需要实力  需要精兵强将
We need muscle,and we need enforcers.
我们需要的是投资回报率
Payback.That's what we need.
老天
God.
我是说  这整个过程简直就是
I mean, this entire process has just been so...
总是这么进一步退两步
It's always been one step forward and two steps back.
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
那我就只能爱之深责之切了  好吗
Let's start with some tough love, all right?
做好心理准备了吗  听听这个
Ready for this?Here goes.
你们俩对兜售毒品实在一窍不通
You two suck at peddling meth.
就是这样
Period.
所以  别想着自己干这个了
So give up on trying to do it all yourselves.
见鬼  我都奇怪你们竟能走到这一步
Hell, I'm amazed you got this far.
我们不想再跟个
Look, we are not going to deal with
高级经销商打交道了
Another high-level distributor.
谢谢了  那条路我们试过了  此路不通
No, thank you.We have been down that road.
什么  你是说那些纹满纹身的瘾君子
What?Some tattooed speed-freak?
你们需要的是个如假包换的商人
Now,what you two need is an honest-to-God businessman.
一个把你们的货
Somebody who treats your product
当高利润日用品一样卖的人
Like the simple high-margin commodity that it is.
一个能做出口  还只做批发的人
Somebody who ships out of town,deals only in bulk.
一个干这行20年
Someone who's been doing this for 20 years
从未失手的人
And never been caught.
你认识这样的人
You know someone like that?
我只能说  我能通过认识的人
Let's just say I know a guy
他再通过认识的人
who knows a guy.
最后才能找上他
Who knows another guy.
容我打几个电话  看看能不能安排你们见见
Let me make some calls,see if I can get you a meeting.
那他叫什么名字
Well, what's his name?
无可奉告
I have no idea.
他行事非常低调
He's very low profile.
就是这么小心谨慎
He's careful like that.
据我所知
From what I do hear about him,
他行事跟你很像
He sounds a little like you.
你得离开这儿
I need you to leave.
听着  有些事
Look, there's...
我有些事瞒着你
Some stuff about me you don't know, and...
譬如说你是个贩毒的
Like you're a drug dealer?
我大概猜到了点
I kind of got that.
你用现金付账  还用个化名  所以
You pay in cash,and you use an alias, so...
我的一个手下
One of my guys,
帮我做事的一个朋友
A friend who worked for me...
被杀了
Got murdered.
是我的错  是我让他去那一带的
It was my fault.I put him on that corner.
我先去吸几口
I'm gonna smoke some crystal,
我就是觉得你该离开这儿  毕竟你
And I just think you should go, being that you're
已经在戒毒了
In a program and all and...
你可以跟我一块去参加戒毒会
You could come with me to a meeting.
不
No
不去戒毒会
No meetings.
或者就这么出去走走也好
We could just get out of here.
-吸毒对你没好处  -不  有用的
- It won't help. - Yeah, it will.
我不需要你来告诉我这些
And I don't need you telling me that it won't.
我只想
I just...
好吧  我只想让你离开这儿
All right, I really just need you to go.
先生
Sir?
祝您用餐愉快
Enjoy your meal.
谢谢
Thank you
你迟到了
You're late.
是啊  这是历史性的时刻
Yeah,We're in the big time now.
那么  我们的主角呢
So where's the kingpin?
我也不知道
Your guess is as good as mine.
那你知道他名字了吗
So you get the dude's name?
不知道
No.
这么说是这样的
So let me get this straight.
他知道我们的名字
He's allowed to know all our names,
知道我们的长相  却没有出现
What we look like,but not the other way around?
你干嘛不去叫点吃的
Why don't you get yourself some food?
这样就不用呆瓜似的
So we won't both sit here with our Happy Meals,
对着开心乐园餐傻坐了吗
Looking like a couple chumps?
两位  一切都还满意吧
Gentlemen,is everything to your satisfaction?
很好  谢谢
Fine, thanks.
除了那个同性恋就没人来过
This is nothing but an ankle-grab.
我不明白  老兄
I don't get you, man.
一周前  你说得好像胸有成竹的样子
A week ago you talked like you were all ready to hang it up.
我们还有差不多40磅的货得卖出去
We've nearly got 40 pounds we still need to sell.
然后呢
What about after?
然后  你还想变什么戏法吗
After, you gonna make up some new magic number?
像什么  "我要钱我要钱我要钱钱钱"
Like, "I got bills. I got bills.I gotta make more."
杰西  你想让我说什么
What do you want me to say, Jesse?
-形势有变  -我想起来了
- Things have changed. - Oh, I know.
我们的人被杀了
We got a guy killed.
你知道吗
You know what?
这都是扯淡
This is bullshit.
我先走一步
I'm out of here.
我想她这是小睡初醒呢
I think she's waking up from a nap.
她肯定急着想出来
She is certainly going to want to get out
好好舒展下手脚了
And stretch those legs soon.
我们得留心着点你的羊水
We'll keep an eye on your fluids.
比正常水平偏低
You're on the low side of normal.
什么  低多少
What? How low?
只要没有急剧下降  就不会有问题
It's not a problem unless we see a growth drop-off,
放心吧
So we're good.
只要下周来做个超声检查
We'll just have you in for an ultrasound next week
最近行动小心点
And keep an eye on things.
老天  你都不知道这一路有多堵
Oh, man, you would not believe the traffic.
所以我提前40分钟出发了
That's why I left 40 minutes early.
抱歉
Sorry.
-我错过什么了吗  -给你贴冰箱上
- What did I miss? - For your refrigerator.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
看看她
Look at her.
快看
Look.
老天  面目栩栩如生呢
God. It's like she's here already.
我刚在跟斯凯勒说  一切都好
I was just telling Skyler everything looks great.
好了  我们商量了几个月了
Okay, we've been talking about it for months now.
该做决定了
It's time to make a decision.
-知道我说的是什么吗  -剖腹产的事吗
- You know what I'm going to say? - The C-section?
如果你们同意的话  我们就排个日程
And if it's a yes,we need to schedule it.
上次分娩的经历太痛苦了  所以
My last labor was pretty tough, so...
为了宝宝  我同意了
For the baby, I say yes.
考虑到你的羊水偏少  我也赞成
I agree, considering that your fluids are on the low side.
最好的话  还是早点动手术
It's best we take her a little early.
这样的话  我们何不排在
So why don't we schedule it for...
下周五怎么样
A week from Friday?
那天不是黑色星期五吧
Isn't that a Friday the 13th?
孩子生日都定好了
We have a birthday.
16号
The 16th.
好日子
I like it.
你知道  说起生日
You know, speaking of birthdays,
我还得回公司一趟  那我们晚点见咯
I've got to run back to the office,so I will see you later?
还有一个小时就下班了
It's an hour before closing.
你不该这么赶来赶去的
You're supposed to be taking it easy.
我们要为泰德的生日小聚一番
We're having a little get-together for Ted's birthday
我还得去取蛋糕
And I've got to pick up the cake.
为什么让你去取
Why you?
因为我说了我去取
Because I said I would.
至少我能做这事吧
It's the least I can do.
-再见  -再见
- Bye.  - Bye.
我们出去逛逛吧
Let's get out of here.
做点什么
You know, go do something.
说真的
Seriously.
记得你说起过的圣达菲博物馆吗
You know that museum in Santa Fe you talked about?
我们去参观下
Let's take a drive.
没问题
Sure.
我不能退还那批原料  都已经钻孔切割了
No I can't return the stock.It's already been drilled and cut
工序都完成一半了
We're halfway through the job.
贝内克先生请到车间来
Mr. Beneke to the shop, please.
行了  让我考虑一下  好吗
All right.Just let me think about it, okay?
我得挂了
I gotta go.
迪安  我得挂电话了
Dean, I gotta go.
生日快乐
Happy Birthday!
天哪  太漂亮了  谢谢大家
My God. This is beautiful, guys.Thank you very much.
快点  这些蜡烛撑不了多久
Hurry. These candles aren't gonna hold out much longer.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你不许愿吗  你得先许愿
Are you making a wish?You gotta make a wish.
好吧让我想想  经济一蹶不振
Ok, well, let's see.The economy's in the toilet.
中国又处处削价竞争  我不知道说啥好了
China's undercutting us at every turn...I'm at a loss.
等等
Wait.
斯凯勒
Skyler
我想先听你唱歌
I want to hear it first.
绝对不行  没门
Absolutely not.No way.
你可不能拒绝老板的生日愿望
You cannot deny your employer his birthday wish.
-是的我可以  看我这样子  -求你了
- Yes, I can. Watch me. - Please!
如果这就是你的生日愿望  我只能说抱歉了
If this is your birthday wish,I feel very, very sorry for you.
-来吧  上次你唱得多好  -那都是陈年往事了
- Come on. It was so good last time. - It was ages ago.
我现在挺着个大肚子
And I'm enormous now.
跟以前判若两人了
And I don't look anything like her anymore.
就是以前也不行啊  拜托
Not that I ever did.I mean, come on.
各位  蜡烛都快燃尽  蜡烛油滴得到处都是了
You guys, these candles are getting wax all over the place.
-答应他吧  -来吧  斯凯勒
- Seriously. - Yes, come on, Skyler.
斯凯勒
Skyler
太难为情了
It's obscene.
祝你生日快乐
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday
贝内克制造公司的老总
Mr. President Of Beneke Fabricators Incorporated
祝你生日快乐
Happy Birthday to you
唱得太好了
That was fantastic.
唱得很棒  对吧
Isn't she great, huh?
好了  吹蜡烛了
Okay, here we go.
-他根本没出现  -他已经在那了
- He wasn't there.- He was there all right.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我坐那等了两个小时  没人来过
I sat there for two hours. Nobody came.
我只知道我的线人说他就在那
All I know is my contact says he was there.
你确定你没走错餐厅吗
Are you sure you were at the right restaurant?
是的  我非常确定
Yes, I'm positive.
-他到底在哪  -谁知道
- Where was he? - Who knows?
也许他一直呆在外面停车场里
Maybe he stayed out in the parking lot,
透过长焦镜头观察着你
Checked you out with a telephoto lens.
又不喜欢你样子
Didn't like the cut of your jib.
话说回来
Anyway,
也无所谓了  我的线人说交易的事黄了
It doesn't matter now because my contact says it's a no go.
什么  你什么意思
What?What do you mean?
黄了  没成
No deal. No dice.
错失良机  不干了
Shot at and missed, shit on and hit.
等一下
Wait a minute.
他怎么能见都不见我们就决定了
How can he make that decision without even meeting me?
我跟你说过  他对选择交易对象非常谨慎
I told you he's very cautious who he does business with.
好吗  他就像鹿一样小心翼翼
All right?He's skittish, like a deer.
把他叫回来
Call him back.
抱歉  我不能这么做
I'm sorry.I can't do that.
你可以的  索尔  打电话给他
Yes, you can.Call him, Saul.
首先  我从没给他打过电话  好吗
First of all,I never called him, all right?
我都是经过好几层才联络上他的
I called a guy who called a guy who called a guy.
其次  这事没戏了
Second of all, it's over.
明白吗  对每个人来说
Understand? With this particular individual,
机会只有一次
All you get is the one shot.
听着  我会想想其他办法
Look,I'll see if I can scrape something else together,
但别抱太大希望
But don't get your hopes up.
没人能像他那样拿下这么大一票货
No one else handles that kind of bulk.
妈的
Damn it.
露西  记得
Lucy, you must remember to
盐瓶 胡椒瓶一定要擦
Have the salt and pepper shakers wiped.
需要什么吗  先生
Can I help you, sir?
健怡可乐  谢谢
Diet Coke, please.
再借用你5分钟时间
And five minutes of your time.
需要效劳吗
What can I do for you?
坐吧
Have a seat.
请坐
Please.
我想知道你昨天为什么不见我
I would like to know why you wouldn't meet with me yesterday.
抱歉  我听不懂
I'm sorry.I'm not following.
我昨天就坐在这儿  等着见一个人
I sat here yesterday,waiting to meet with someone.
我相信那个人就是你
I believe that person was you.
我想你认错人了
I think that you're confusing me for someone else.
我不这么认为
I don't think I am.
先生  如果您有任何不满
Sir, if you have a complaint,
建议您通过电子邮件提交
I suggest you submit it through our e-mail system.
我很乐意帮您上传到我们的网站
I would be happy to refer you to our website.
有人告诉我  我要见的这个人
I was told that the man I would be meeting with
行事非常小心
Is very careful.
是个谨慎的人
A cautious man.
我相信这点上我们很像
I believe we're alike in that way.
如果我猜得没错
If you are who I think you are,
你就该再给我一次机会
You should give me another chance.
我不认为我们有什么像的  怀特先生
I don't think we're alike at all, Mr. White.
你根本就不是个谨慎的人
You are not a cautious man at all.
你的搭档迟到了  他还吸毒
Your partner was late, and he was high.
是的
Yes, he was.
他毒瘾很重  是吗
He's high often, isn't he?
你判断力太差
You have poor judgment.
我不能跟判断力这么差的人共事
I can't work with someone with poor judgment.
你对我生产的货了解吗
Are you familiar with my product?
据说非常赞
I've been told it's excellent.
那是毋庸置疑的
It is impeccable.
绝对是最纯的
It is the purest,
放到市面上绝对供不应求
Most chemically-sound product on the market anywhere.
我可以找其他人要货
That is not the only factor.
以我目前的定价
You could charge twice
你还可以翻一番卖
The current rate for what I provide,
他们照样会买
And your customers would pay it.
易如反掌
Hands down.
我选谁跟我一起做买卖
Now, who I choose to do business with on my end
那不关你的事
Is not your problem.
你不用见他
You won't see him.
不用跟他联系
You won't interact with him.
就当他不存在
Forget he exists.
我不得不问一句
I have to ask.
为什么
Why?
因为他对我言听计从
Because he does what I say.
因为我能信任他
Because I can trust him.
你们手头有多少货
How much product do you have on hand?
38磅
38 pounds.
准备一次出清
Ready to go at a moment's notice.
我怎么听你的答复
Will I hear from you?
我有你的号码
I have your numbers.
永远不要信任吸毒的人
You can never trust a drug addict.
看  都是各种名目的零星支出
Look, I mean, it's all kind of little dribs and drabs,
但是这里  以凯勒公司为例
But right here,take Keller, for instance.
这边几百  那边几千的
A couple hundred dollars here,a few thousand there.
都是零星支出
Dribs and drabs.
一旦加起来  单单凯勒公司一项
Once you add it all up, though,and with Keller,
就比应缴税额少交了将近10%
The revenues are almost 10% less than was actually received.
过去两年每个季度都是这样
And this is every quarter,for the last two years.
我看到之后  觉得很担心
When I saw that, I got worried
所以我查了下其他客户的应收账款
So I checked Accounts Receivable on other customers.
发现还有其他六家的账款短报了
I found six other instances of revenues being under-reported.
而这只是刚刚开始查
And I've only just started to look into it.
我们跟很多这样的公司订立了需求合约
We have requirement contracts with a lot of these companies.
他们会预估下一季的需求给我们
They anticipate their needs for the next quarter.
多数时候  他们会高估一点
Most of the time, they overestimate.
所以我就把高估的部分  滚动计入下张订单
So I just let them roll their overages into the next order
不然的话  客户就会流失
And if I don't,they'll go elsewhere.
很明显  我们疏忽了
Obviously, we forgot
没回溯过去调整收入记录
And didn't go back and adjust the revenue entries.
我知道站在会计的角度
I know it's wrong from an accounting standpoint,
这是不对的
But as you can see,
但你可以看到  最终钱还是进账了
The money's coming in ventually.As you can see.
对
Right.
是的  但是
Right, but...
我在储藏室拿了以前的销售单据和订购单
I got the old bills of sale and order forms out of storage,
想分一下类
To try and sort this out.
多数时候
And most of the time,
根本就没有收入记录的备份
There's no backup for the reported revenues at all.
有些文件中
In a few cases,
我发现了数据涂改过的影印件
I found Xeroxed copies with the dates changed.
泰德
Ted
好吧
All right.
被你逮到了
You got me.
这可是将近一百万美金的未申报收入
We're talking nearly a million dollars of undocumented revenue.
-你到底在想些什么  -我想的是
- What are you thinking? - I'm thinking
挽救这个公司
About saving a company.
想着保住工人们的工作
I'm thinking about people's jobs,
想着他们的房贷和退休金
About their mortgages and pensions
还有他们孩子的大学学费
And their college funds for their kids.
更别提还有我自己
Not to mention my own.
这并不意味着你就得犯法
It doesn't mean that you have to break the law.
对  就是这样
Yes, it does.
这些账目里都写着呢  生意难做啊
It's right there in the books.Business is terrible.
银行来找我麻烦  国税局恨不得把我榨干
The bank is on my back,the IRS is grinding me down to a nub.
如果我撑不下去
If I don't keep up...
泰德  这样会坐牢的
Ted,people go to prison for this.
我爸爸白手起家成立这家公司
My dad built this company from nothing.
我们在这里做事赚钱
We make things here.
在这工作的人们  就像家人一样
The people who work here are like family.
我不能因为这几年年景不好
I can't let that all fall apart
就让一切分崩离析
Because of a couple of bad years.
斯凯勒
Skyler
别告发我
Don't report this.
求你了
Please.
我不会去告发你的 泰德
I'm not gonna turn you in Ted
但我不能参与进来
But I can't be a part of it.
我知道
I know.
我知道  我只希望
I know. I just wish...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不想让你走
I don't want you to go.
认识我的话  留言吧
Yo, if I know you, leave a message.
我是瘦子彼得  就打电话看看你怎么了  兄弟
Yo, it's Skinny Pete.Just checking in with you, man.
今天在葬礼上没看到你
We missed you at the funeral today.
大家都去了
The whole crew was representing.
连猴子都从弗雷斯诺赶了回来
Even Badger came all the way from Fresno.
康宝的家人  他的妈妈  奶奶  侄子们
Combo's people, his ma,grandma,cousins,
每个人都哭成泪人了
Everyone was all choked up and shit.
兄弟  那可真是  催人泪下
Man, it was, like, emotional.
你真该来看看那口棺材
And you should have seen the coffin.
涂着白色珠光漆  闪闪发亮
It was like this shiny,white pearlescent.
我确保在一辆雷克萨斯车上
Like,I'm pretty sure
见过一摸一样的油漆工艺
I've seen the exact same paint job on a Lexus.
所以肯定是非常高级的
So we're definitely talking high-end.
当然  我猜你肯定有更重要的事走不开
Anyway, guess you had something bigger going down.
那你自己一切小心了  兄弟  保重
Watch your back out there, bro.Peace.
我喜欢在里面混一些冰毒
I like to mix some ice with it.
拿着
Hold that.
那是什么感觉
What's it feel like?
会打冷颤
There's a chill.
别怕  很快就过去的
Don't freak out.It passes.
然后
And then...
你就等着吧
You'll see.
我会来陪你的
I'll meet you there.
把那个拿走
Take that off.
请把手机都关掉
Phones off, please.
我猜是管道的声音
Pipes, I guess.
好了各位  看着自己的试卷
All right, everyone.Eyes on your paper.
都看着自己的试卷
Eyes on your paper.
短信:快餐店见
打扰一下  经理上哪去了
Excuse me, where's the manager?
我就是经理  有事吗
I'm the manager.Can I help you?
我上周在这见过个男的  黑人绅士
I met a man here last week.A black gentleman.
很瘦戴眼镜的
He's thin. Glasses.
是的  先生  那是店主
Yes, sir.That's the owner.
他在这和内华达州拥有14家洛博罗餐厅
He owns 14 Los Pollos restaurants in between here and Nevada.
可能在其中任意一家
He could be at any one of them.
有没有他的手机号码  我可以
Is there a phone number that I can get to...
抱歉  先生  我不便透露
I'm sorry, sir.I can't give that out.
您是有什么投诉吗
Is this about a complaint?
我很乐意帮您提交到我们网站上去
I'd be happy to refer you to our website.
不 不是
No no
-他叫什么名字  -古斯塔沃
- What's his name? - Gustavo.
古斯
Gus.
谢谢
Thank you
38磅货  120万美金
38 pounds, $1.2 million.
25号公路13号出口往南2公里处的车站交易
Truck stop,2 miles south of exit 13 on the 25.
一小时后交易
One hour.
-什么  -一个小时  你干不干
- What?- One hour. You in or out?
干  当然干  但得多给我点时间准备
In. In. Absolutely.But I just need a little more time.
一个小时  如果你人没到
One hour.If you miss it,
下次就别上这儿来了
Don't ever show your face in here again.
25号公路  13号出口往南  有个车站
Exit 13 off the 25 South,to a truck...
-接电话  快接电话  -认识我的话  留言吧
- Come on! Come on! - Yo, if I know you, leave a message.
杰西  快接电话
Jessi,Pick up the phone.
快接电话呀
Pick up the phone!
我正在赶过去  我去取货
I'm coming by.I need the product.
现在就需要那批货
I need the product now!
老天
God
杰西
Jessi
斯凯勒来电
Incoming Call Skyler
杰西
Jessi
杰西  醒醒
Jessi Wake up!
杰西
Jessi
醒醒
Wake up.
你把货放哪了
Where'd you put it?
-货在哪  货藏哪了  -放开我
- Where is it? Where's the product? - Get off of me.
货在哪  你把货藏哪了
Where is it?Where'd you hide the meth?
-厨房里  -厨房哪里
- In the kitchen. - Where?
水槽下面
Under the sink.
短信: 孩子要生了
别是现在啊
Not now!